<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Team09 Project</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_secondpage">secondpage</string>
    <string name="tempearature">Temperature</string>
    <string name="condition">Condition</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_alarm">AlarmActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nutrient_chart">NutrientChart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_share_text">ShareTextActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_run">MyRun</string>
    <string name="title_activity_my_settings">MySettings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bar_graph">BarGraph</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="case1">
       "INGRID RINCK\n\n"
        "When Ingrid was pregnant with her third child, she went through some difficult personal issues, turned to food to soothe herself, and watched as the number on the scale went up…and up and up. In all, she gained 100 pounds. "I basically self-medicated with food," she says.\n\n"

        "After giving birth, she vowed to find a sustainable way to lose the pounds. For her, that mean not depriving herself of any one food group, instead eating until she felt satisfied, not stuffed."I ate three meals a day with small portions," she explains. "They consisted of mostly lean protein, carbs, healthy fats, and vegetables. And I changed my view of food — from looking at it as a source of pleasure to seeing it as a source of fuel for my body."/n/n"

        "In 3 months, she dropped 40 pounds, and her energy levels and stamina skyrocketed. By the 8-month mark, she'd lost all 100 pounds. "Make vision boards of where you want to be and what you want to look at," she advises. (Hers contained goal-oriented images: a healthy family, outfits she eventually planned to wear, and beach vacations.) "Looking at these boards on a daily basis trains your mind to see you as that fit, healthy person," she adds.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="case2">
        "TIFFANY ERIN HUMPHRIES\n\n"
        "For 15 years, Tiffany found the pounds adding up and her unhappiness growing, but she couldn\'t find the spark she needed to overhaul her life. "Many things happened through those years that you\'d think would be a trigger to lose weight — from having to do the \'walk of shame\' at Six Flags because I couldn\'t fit on the ride to getting a seat belt extender on an airplane," Tiffany says. "But one day, I just thought, I want to live a long life and see my daughter grow up."\n\n"

        "In January 2016, she joined Weight Watchers and, through healthier food choices and a new commitment to jogging, the pounds flew off. "Now I\'m running 5Ks, and my family is leading a healthier life," she says. She\'s lost 102 pounds and shrunk from about a size 22 to a size 6. "This past year has flown by and I am enjoying life more and more," she says. "Time needs to slow down so I can soak it all in!"\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="case3">
        "AUDREY MCLAUGHLIN \n\n"
        "This once athletic nurse knew she needed to lose weight when she realized she was tired, unhappy, and "most importantly, out of love with myself," she recalls. Now, she\'s lost 45 pounds and is still losing, all with one simple change: mindful eating. "Don\'t worry about the time of day you are hungry," she advises. "Get over breakfast is at 7, lunch is at 12, dinner is at 7. It doesn\'t matter." Instead of sticking to set mealtimes, Audrey only eats when she\'s hungry ("around a 7 on a 0-10 scale") and stops when she's no longer peckish — not stuffed. As she eats, she takes regular check-ins to see where she falls on the hunger scale. To work on mindful eating, apps like Headspace have helpful guided meditations. \n\n"
    </string>
</resources>
